Jack Curtin

About

Throughout my life I have been guided by my passions for creative expression. Connecting with others driven by the same spirit keeps me motivated and inspired. I'm ready to throw myself full-force into my next role, contributing strong programming and organizational skills, sales experience, and an eagerness to collaborate and connect.

Contact

T: (803) 429-5387

jackcurtin94@gmail.com

2527 N Monticello Ave Apt 2R Chicago, IL 60647



Experience

Move-tastic!

Apr 2020 - Mar 2021

IT Technician / Customer Service Representative

Regularly performed maintenance on tablets and other technology devices used in the field, as well as tracked and optimized computer and network health in the office. Drafted personalized estimates based on client-provided information. Managed scheduling clients and staffing the movers, tailoring crews that would best fit the client's needs. Worked with clients to settle any damage claims opened up after their move. Assisted potential clients through email or phone correspondence with any inquiries about the company's services, as well as made any adjustments for current clients.

Reckless Records

Oct 2017 - Mar 2020

Floor Manager / Used Product Buyer

Worked with other employees in determining a fair price to offer the seller that corresponds with our used product margin. Dealt closely with customers when paying them out and explaining our process of purchasing . As floor manager, responsibilities included opening/closing the store each shift, counting the money, and filling out the necessary paperwork. Also handled retail and customer service responsibilities.

Loyola University ITS

May 2014 - Jan 2017

Network Security Intern / Help Desk Technician

Worked with students to troubleshoot network connection issues and solve problems they were having with their personal devices. Assisted in the maintenance of ethernet and cable ports across campus.



Education

General Assembly

Mar 2021 - May 2021

Loyola University Chicago
Bachelor's in Film and Digital Media

Software Engineering Immersive

Graduated May 2017

Universidad Alberto Huertado

Summer 2016

Studied abroad in Santiago, Chile Documentary Production

Skills

Programming Knowledge

- Junior level full-stack development with Angular and Spring Boot
- · Familiarity with PostgreSQL, Docker, Jenkins, and Heroku

Software Experience

- Proficiency of Adobe Premiere, Audition, & G-Suite programs
- Adept Knowledge of Adobe Photoshop & In Design

Independent Projects & Passions

- Self-produced documentaries, short films, photography, and music
- · Available to view at thoroughlybad.com/jackcurtin